Come on, get on up
We're wild and we can't be tamed
And we're turnin' the floor into
A zoo, ooh, ooh
Hop-ah, hop-ah, hop-ah, hop-ah, ah Hop-ah, hop-ah, oh
We live in a crazy world, caught up in a rat race
Concrete jungle life is sometimes a mad place
It's you and me together at the end of a wild day
Don't keep it all bottled up, and release your energy
Hey, oh-ayy, only reason we are here is to celebrate
In a place where anyone can be anything
Hold on to this moment, don't let it fade away
Baby, keep the music playin'
Come on, get on up
We're wild and we can't be tamed
And we're turnin' the floor into
A zoo, ooh, ooh
Come on, keep it up
It's fun if you're down to play
And we're turnin' the floor into
A zoo, ooh, ooh